egress.com 2015-05-11

# Privacy Statement | Egress Switch

This policy sets out the basis on which personal data collected from you, or that you provide to us will be processed by us. This policy is in addition to additional obligations relating to your personal data contained in the specific terms and conditions that you may enter into with us in respect of our delivery and your receipt of the Egress Switch Services.

**1\. EGRESS SOFTWARE TECHNOLOGIES LIMITED**

Egress Software Technologies Limited is a company registered in England and Wales with its place of business at Unit 16, Quadrant Business Centre, 135 Salusbury Road, London NW6 6RJ. 

**2\. PERSONAL DATA COLLECTED FROM YOU**

**2.1** The personal data which we collect from you are as follows: 

  * your name; 
  * your geographical address; 
  * your email address,  
(collectively, " **Your Personal Data** "). 

  * If you decide to upgrade your free subscription to a paying subscription which requires you to provide banking and payment information, then we will also collect banking and payment information from you (" **Billing Information** ").

**2.2** If you have provided us with the personal data of another person (" **Third Party Personal Data** ") you confirm that they consent to the processing of their personal data by us and that you have informed them of our identity and the purposes (as set out herein and in any agreement between us) for which their personal data will be processed.

**2.3** If you have provided us with Billing Information you thereby consent to the collection and processing of payments by Egress Software Technologies Ltd, or by a third party payments service provider acting on Egress Software Technologies Ltd's behalf, to process or deliver orders, invoices, or notify you of the status of your order made via our website. No other use is made of your Billing Information, nor is it stored by us other than for use as set out in this paragraph 2.3.

**3\. USES MADE OF YOUR PERSONAL DATA**

**3.1** Your Personal Data shall be kept confidential by us. 

**3.2** We will use Your Personal Data: 

  * to enable us to provide the services which we have agreed to provide to you; 
  * to alert you to any product and service changes and updated information; and
  * for our own administration purposes.

**3.3** In the event you do not wish for us to use Your Personal Data for alerting purposes, please either 

  * click on the "Unsubscribe" link in the emails we have sent you (if any); or
  * email us at support@egress.com and notify us of your request for us not to contact you.

**3.4** We shall not pass Your Personal Data to any third party for marketing purposes (including our marketing affiliates and partners) unless we have procured your express consent to do so.

**4\. RETENTION OF YOUR PERSONAL DATA**

**4.1** In respect of Your Personal Data for which we are the Data Controller (as defined in the Data Protection Act 1998 (the " **Act** ")) we will comply in all regards with our obligations under the Act including taking all appropriate measures to ensure that any Your Personal Data is kept secure and kept for only so long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Policy. 

**4.2** In respect of Your Personal Data for which you are the Data Controller and we are the Data Processor (as defined in the Act), we will comply in all regards with our obligations under the Act, including complying with the detailed obligations set out in the relevant terms and conditions that we have agree with you.

**4.3** If Your Personal Data changes, please notify Egress Software Technologies Limited by contacting us by writing to Egress Software Technologies Limited at Unit 16, Quadrant Business Centre, 135 Salusbury Road, London NW6 6RJ or emailing us at [info@egress.com](mailto:info@egress.com). We will update Your Personal Data within seven (7) working days of any new or updated personal data being provided to us, to ensure that the personal data we hold about you is as accurate and up to date as possible.

**5\. YOUR RIGHTS**

**5.1** You are entitled to ask for a copy of any personal data that we hold about you (for which we may charge a small fee) and to have any inaccuracies in your personal data corrected. If you wish to contact us for these purposes, please email us at [info@egress.com](mailto:info@egress.com). 

**5.2** The website may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

**6\. DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION**

**6.1** We may disclose Your Personal Data and/or Billing Information to any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries.

**6.2** We may disclose Your Personal Data and/or Billing Information to third parties only in the following limited situations: 

  * if Egress Software Technologies Limited or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by Egress Software Technologies Limited may be transferred to the entity acquiring Egress Software Technologies Limited; or
  * if we are under a duty to disclose or share Your Personal Data in order to comply with any legal or regulatory obligation, or in order to enforce any of our agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Egress Software Technologies Limited, our customers, or third parties. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection.

**7\. COOKIES AND IP ADDRESSES**

**7.1** We may store information about you in a cookie (a small file that is sent by our web server to your computer), which we can access when you make return visits to www.egress.com (the " **Website** "). Storing cookies is usual practice for any web site that needs to remember what its users' preferences are and we use cookies to keep track of your choices in the Website.

**7.2** If you would like to delete any cookies that are already on your computer, please refer to the instructions for your file management software to locate the file or directory that cookies are stored in. If you would like to stop cookies being stored on your computer in the future, please refer to your browser manufacturer's instructions by clicking "Help" in your browser menu. Further information about deleting or controlling cookies is available at [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/).

**7.3** Please note that when you visit our site, we may also log your IP address, a unique identifier for your computer or other access device.

**8\. CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY**

**8.1** Any changes we may make to this Privacy Policy document in the future will be posted on this page and notified to you using our Website.

**9\. CONTACT DETAILS**

Please direct any queries about this Privacy Policy to

Egress Software Technologies Limited   
Unit 16, Quadrant Business Centre   
135 Salusbury Road  
London NW6 6RJ
